[
  {
    "id": "548",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A way to access other AWS services using the AWS network without having to send traffic over the public internet",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "NACL",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["VPC Endpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "549",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ increase security and allow AWS services to communicate privately and reliably",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "NACL",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["VPC Endpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "550",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Two types of VPC endpoints (Select 2)",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "NACL",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "550",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "This type of VPC endpoint uses a private DNS entry",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "NACL",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Interface endpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "551",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "This type of VPC endpoint is also known as PrivateLink",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "NACL",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Interface endpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "552",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "This type of VPC endpoint is only available for DynamoDB and S3",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "NACL",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Gateway endpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "553",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "This type of VPC endpoint uses a route table entry",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "NACL",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Gateway endpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "554",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ are internet enabled by default",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "SageMaker Notebook Instances",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SageMaker Notebook Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "555",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Internet enabled, ______ are allowed to download and access to popular packages and libraries",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "SageMaker Notebook Instances",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SageMaker Notebook Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "556",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Internet enabled, ______ are allowed to download and access to popular packages and libraries",
      "answers": [
        "VPC Endpoint",
        "VPC",
        "Interface endpoint",
        "Gateway endpoint",
        "SageMaker Notebook Instances",
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SageMaker Notebook Instances"]
    }
  }
]